John Robert M. Aman



Web Developer/IT Support

Lucena City, Philippines 4301

09266626071

☑ Johnaman201@gmail.com

https://github.com/johnaman201

https://johnaman.herokuapp.com/

in https://linkedin.com/in/johnaman1211

I have 2 years of experience building and developing various web applications. I am consistently open to learning and strive to build new skills. Currently, I am working on web applications using technologies like JavaScript, HTML5, CSS3 React, Tailwind, PHP, and MySQL.

Professional Experience

Michelene's Mart - San Miguel Distributor. Lucena City, Philippines

Analyze and diagnose computer issues. I also monitor processing functions, install relevant software and perform tests on computer equipment and applications when necessary. Install and troubleshoot computer hardware and software. I also created and developed the company Human Resources Management System (HRMS) and Store Distribution system

- · CCTV installation and monitoring
- · Remotely installing software and troubleshooting
- Maintaining and monitoring company computer system
- Accountable in a timely manner to service issues and requests
- Providing technical support across the company (this may be in person or over the phone)
- Repair and replace equipment as necessary
- Testing new technologies
- Installing and configuring Linux SUSE for POS
- Installing the latest Anti-virus version on all site/clients' devices
- Ensuring stable operation of the computer networks LAN/WLAN.
- Installs, configures, and maintains multi-user software to be accessed from file servers using Synology drive.
- Develops front-end websites using HTML5, CSS3 and JavaScript
- Back-end development utilizing PHP and MySQL for the database to maintain website integrity
- PHP framework CodeIgniter and Laravel

2020-07 – 2020-11 Full-Stack Web Developer

Maryhill College, Inc. Lucena City, Philippines

Design the appearance, navigation, and content organization of a website. Utilize HTML, CSS, PHP, JavaScript, and MySQL support to manage graphics, applications, and content that address a school's needs. Implemented changes and integrated the requested elements to streamline business operations.

- Provided security maintenance and patching on website interface to maintain viability after launch
- cPanel Domain Management

2019-09 – 2020-01 **IT Support**

HiRecruit BPO. Lucena City, Philippines

Responsible for reviewing and solving computer network and hardware problems for the company. Provide general support to a company's employees and technical support on user experience issues that require technical assistance. Facilitate repairs and upgrades on laptops, mobile phones, printers, and CCTVs

2019-01 – 2019-04 Web Developer Intern

PASIA, Procurement and Supply Institute of Asia- GPAS Makati City, Philippines

My tasks are to design and construct websites. And ensure that sites meet user expectations by ensuring they look good, run smoothly, and offer easy access points with no loading issues between pages or error messages. Using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and PHP.

Education

2015-06 - 2019-07

Bachelor of Science in Information Technology

(MSEUF) Manuel S. Enverga University Foundation, Lucena City, Philippines

Certifications



The Complete Full-Stack JavaScript Course!

StackSkills

Issued Jul 2022 · No Expiration Date



JavaScript Beginner Bootcamp 2022

StackSkills

Issued Apr 2022 · No Expiration Date



Microsoft Technology Associate: Windows Operating System Fundamentals (MTA)

Microsoft

Issued Dec 2017 · No Expiration Date